The Postcard Killings is a drama, thriller film directed by Danis Tanović.
After suffering a personal tragedy, and desperate for justice, Jacob Kanon, a veteran New York City police detective,
embarks on the search for a twisted killer who is leaving a bloody trail of elaborate murders across Europe.
Jacob Kanon, played by Jeffrey Dean Morgan.
Valerie Kanon, played by Famke Janssen.
Dessie Lombard, played by Cush Jumbo.
Inspector Klaus Bublitz, played by Joachim Król.
Detective Inspector Rupert Pierce, played by Steven Mackintosh.
Marina Haysmith / Sylvia Randolph, played by Naomi Battrick.
The Postcard Killings is a 2020 American crime film directed by Danis Tanović, starring Jeffrey Dean Morgan, Famke
Janssen and Cush Jumbo, and based on the 2010 novel The Postcard Killers by James Patterson and Liza Marklund.
The film was released on March 13, 2020,
receiving negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of london, england, based on novel or book,
family secrets, stockholm, sweden, serial killer.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.